the strategic innovation group is really structured
in order to provide can create new value for our clients
a lot of people say well what exactly do you mean by that
when you think about where we are at this point in history
the budgets across all of government
and even our commercial clients are declining operational budgets to perform
their mission
or to accomplish their business objectives and yet
when you think about it the requirements
the expectations and those missions and businesses have not changed
anyway and so our clients across the board are really looking for ways to
create new value
from ideas from innovations from new capabilities put together in new ways
that's really what this strategic Innovation Group Inc who's now on
is focused on providing for our clients
by bringing capabilities and innovations together in new and unique ways
in some cases their old ideas put together in new ways
in some cases their new ideas but in
either dimension and we're looking at ways to bring those ideas to create
solutions that help our clients solve their most challenging problems
and the reality years with less money to spend they need those product they need
those
problem solved in a more efficient way than ever before
so when you think about declining budgets and yet increasing expectations
for mission in business
there's a gap between what our clients can afford
and what they need and we're calling Matt the value gap
and from the value gap what we're trying to do
is create new solutions for our clients that are less expensive
access existing or new emerging take not technologies and combine them with
existing capabilities to provide
better solutions than what they've had previously so hopefully we're creating
new value for our clients by doing that
our capabilities are combined in unique ways
we have structured our innovation agenda very purposefully
along are clients most challenging and pressing problems
me give you an example in a few of those all of our clients
are suffering from an inundation I have data
but they don't have to manage it they don't really know what data they have
they don't have stored and most importantly they don't have to get value
from it
SAR Bali from data initiative is specifically focused on developing
products and services for clients
they can leverage their latent data across their institution
to better manage their institution or their firms other business
but most importantly also to generate value from that data
in it in no way of products and services
we're also working on a big client problem around being able to predict
threats whether it's insider threats are global threats
to commercial businesses or to our government clients
in in touch today
what we see is clients being able to
react to threats but not necessarily be able to predict
when and where and how they might occur
are foresight capabilities
global foresight cyber force I'd and insider foresight
are specific capabilities and solutions that we've tailored from our years of
working with the intelligence community
to help commercial clients and other government clients better predict where
those threats might happen
our clients across the board have massive
numbers systems many redundant many outdated
interfacing modernization challenges that are facing
inherent use challenges across their
organization as well as
issues with regard to their effectiveness in supporting the mission
our mission solutions initiative is focused
vary purposefully on helping our clients solve their enterprise systems problems
by creating more tactical useful
forward-deployed systems debt eliminate outdated a redundant systems
but also takin a value of new emerging technologies
it's interesting when as a part of the twenty20
vision we decided to stand up the strategic innovation group it was
important to me as its first leader
that we be very focused on not just creating ideas
and innovations but in creating
in building business and specifically the business
the future the firm and a key part a bad
is our continued collaboration with our market in our account colleagues
when you think about the value of booze now on
our value has always been that we are major ext organization
that we develop and drive
the most exciting and emerging capabilities
across the institution into multiple accounts and markets
and sell their strategic innovation group is very focused on continuing to
do that
so when we talk about our innovation agenda that information age ended
is key and dependent upon working with our market America count colleagues who
understand the domains have defense
security commercial in this civil markets
far better than we do but we understand our capabilities we know the
technologies we know the ideas that were developing we know the problems were
trying to solve so that combination Inc lab racin between the
Innovation Group and the market group is key to our success
and key to building is future businesses